# **Jack Funck**

Front-End, Back-End, and Fullstack Developer

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/jackfunckGitHub: https://github.com/JFunck1990

> Portfolio: https://ifunck1990.github.io/HW-2-Responsive-Portfolio/

Hello! My name is John Funck, most call me Jack. I am hoping to get in with your team as an entry level front-end or Full Stack Web Developer. In May of 2021 I have earned a certificate in full stack development from the University of North Carolina, where I have obtained skills in JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React.js, Jquery, API Interaction (API, JSON, Ajax), Databases(MySQL and MongoDB), Server Side Development, and Quality Assurance. In December of 2013 I graduated from Western Carolina University with a BS degree in Entrepreneurship. Since graduating I worked for various companies where I have obtained skills in Customer Service, Leadership, and problem solving. I am excited to leverage my new skills and work with a great team!

#### Projects:

- The-Burger-Log| <a href="https://github.com/JFunck1990/The-Burger-Log">https://github.com/JFunck1990/The-Burger-Log</a> |
  <a href="https://the-burger-logger.herokuapp.com/">https://the-burger-logger.herokuapp.com/</a> |
- Post N' Stuff | <a href="https://github.com/JFunck1990/Posts-n-Stuff">https://github.com/JFunck1990/Posts-n-Stuff</a> | <a href="https://postnstuff.herokuapp.com/">https://postnstuff.herokuapp.com/</a> |
- The Note Taker | <a href="https://github.com/JFunck1990/The-Note-Taker">https://github.com/JFunck1990/The-Note-Taker</a> | <a href="https://agile-waters-80427.herokuapp.com/">https://agile-waters-80427.herokuapp.com/</a> |

**EXPERIENCE** 

### **American Airlines**, Charlotte NC — Fleet Service Agent/D1 Level

January 2015 - PRESENT

- Leading teams to get a planes out on time
- Making sure customers baggage is safe and loaded
- Keeping track of dangerous goods

#### **Faithful Companion**, Charlotte NC — Operations Assistant/Driver

May 2014 - December 2014

- Provided comfort for those who lost their pet
- Made sure pets are picked up and dropped off in a timely manner.
- Performed the cremation process

## Ranger Construction, Charlotte NC — Assistant Superintendent

January 2005 - September 2016

• Helped Superintendents with Plumbing, Electrical work, and Concrete work.

4500 Wentworth pl Charlotte,NC,28209 (704) 400-4431 jackfunck21@gmail.co

#### **SKILLS**

- > HTML
- > CSS
- > JavaScript
- > Jquery
- >Deployment/Comman d-Line Fundamentals (Heroku, Git, GitHub Pages)
- >API Interaction (API, JSON, AJax)
- >MySQL
- >MongoDB
- >Server Side Development
- >Quality Assurance
- >Customer Service
- > Leadership

### Rugby Athletic Center, Charlotte NC — Facilities Management Assistant

January 2013 - May 2014

- Assisted with Landscaping Management
- Assisted with concession sales (Cashier, making food products and serving food products)
- products)Parking Management
- Ticket Sales

#### **EDUCATION**

# **The University of North Carolina**, Chapel Hill NC — *Certificate in Full-Stack-Development*

November 2020 - May 2021

The Coding Boot Camp at UNC-Chapel Hill is a part-time, Full Stack Flex course where I have obtained skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, and much more.

## **Western Carolina University**, Cullowhee NC — *Bachelor's Degree in Entrepreneurship* **September 2011 - December 2013**

Gained skills in HTML, CSS, Business Management, Finance, and Marketing.

## Mars Hill University, Mars Hill NC — Biology/ transferred to WCU September 2009 - May 2011

## Leadership/Volunteering:

- >LAWA Fundraising Volunteer(Latin America Women's Association)
- > Eagle Scout, Boy Scouts of America
- > Athletic Director, Pi Kappa PHi Fraternity
- > U-15 South Charlotte Rugby, Assistant Coach
- > CMS Volunteer, Huntingtown Farms Elementary Tutor